{
  "questions_dangers_internet": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "You should share your password",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "An HTTPS website is 100% guaranteed to be safe",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "An app can sell your data without permission",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "Why should you use a strong password?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "To avoid being hacked"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "What is a sign that your data has been hacked?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "Suspicious emails, unknown logins, modified accounts"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "What does 'ransomware' mean?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Malware that locks your files for a ransom"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "What is a common online danger?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Phishing", "Surfing", "Shopping"],
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "Phishing"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "Phishing consists of...",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Stealing the wifi", "Cooking fish", "Stealing passwords"],
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "Stealing passwords"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "theme": "Dangers of the internet",
      "question": "What is a sign that a Wi-Fi network has been compromised?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Unknown devices", "Long password", "Weak signal"],
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Unknown devices"
    }
  ],

  "questions_artificial_intelligence": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "AI can recognize images",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "AI can learn on its own without data",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "Generative AI can create completely original content",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "What do you call a machine that learns from examples?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "Machine learning"
    },

    {
      "id": 5,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "What is the role of a dataset?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "Generative"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "What do you call an AI that generates original content from examples?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "To provide training data"
    },
        {
      "id": 7,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "Artificial intelligence",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Make coffee", "Analyze data", "Cook"],
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "Analyze data"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "Artificial intelligence",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Assisted intelligence", "Artificial intelligence", "Advanced Interface"],
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "Artificial intelligence"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "theme": "Artificial Intelligence",
      "question": "Artificial intelligence",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Medicine", "Agriculture", "Telecommunications"],
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "all of them"
    }
  ]
  ,
  "questions_general_knowledge": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "YouTube belongs to Google",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "What symbol is used in hashtags?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "hash, diese"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "What is the most well-known search engine?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Google", "Bing", "Yahoo"],
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "The first social networks used videos to communicate",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "In which year was YouTube created?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "2005"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "Who invented the World Wide Web?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Bill Gates", "Tim Berners-Lee", "Steve Jobs"],
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "The first website ever created is still online?",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "In which programming language was Minecraft created in 2009?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Java"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "theme": "General knowledge on the internet",
      "question": "What was the first globally popular social network?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Facebook", "MySpace", "Instagram"],
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "MySpace"
    }
  ],
  "questions_utility_applications": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "Free apps never collect data",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "An app can keep using your location in the background",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "An app can install software without permission",
      "type": "True or false",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "What is Google Maps used for?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "answer": "Finding your way and getting directions"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "TikTok is mainly known for...",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Short videos", "Emails", "Longs videos"],
      "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "What percentage of websites are created using WordPress?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "answer": "43% (accepted if “around 40%” or “1 out of 2” is said)"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "What kind of data can an app collect without you noticing?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Location, cookies, device IDs, usage habits"
 
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "What type of data can an app silently collect?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Your deleted photos", "Your printed documents", "Your contacts"],
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Your contacts"


    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "theme": "Utility applications",
      "question": "Which app is the most used for collaborative work?",
      "type": "Multiple choice",
      "options": ["Trello", "Notion", "Teams"],
      "difficulty": 3,
      "answer": "Teams"
    }
  ],
  "questions_good_luck": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "What is the first YouTube video?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "Me at the zoo"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "How to recognize mail phishing?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "email address, spelling mistakes"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "Why can too much data be harmful for AI?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "because it can create error"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "Which software compressed or decompresses files easily?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "WinRAR"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "Which animated image format, created in 1987, still dominates the internet?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "GIF"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "What do you call an attack that requires no user click?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "zero-click"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "What is the name for the data used to evaluate a model?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "test set"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "Which software compresses multiple files into one archive?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "WinZip"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "What is considered the first video game ever made?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "Pong"  
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "What type of attack overloads a website until it crashes?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "DDoS"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "AI that learns without supervision?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "unsupervised"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "theme": "Good luck",
      "question": "Which tool secures a home Wi-Fi network?",
      "type": "Open question",
      "difficulty": null,
      "answer": "Firewall"
    }
  ]
}